{
    "subject": "Sirikit",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Bhumibol_Adulyadej",
    "human_readable": "Sirikit is married to Bhumibol Adulyadej.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9876433610916138,
            "question": "Is there a known marriage between Sirikit and Bhumibol Adulyadej?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9360544085502625,
            "question": "Who was the spouse of Bhumibol Adulyadej?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9309877157211304,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Sirikit and Bhumibol Adulyadej?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9050428867340088,
            "question": "Is Sirikit married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9001907706260681,
            "question": "Who was Bhumibol Adulyadej's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8913870453834534,
            "question": "Who is Sirikit married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8411901593208313,
            "question": "What is the name of Bhumibol Adulyadej's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8323990702629089,
            "question": "What is the name of Bhumibol Adulyadej's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7052006125450134,
            "question": "To whom is Sirikit connected in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6180781722068787,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Sirikit's marital status?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sirikit is married to Bhumibol Adulyadej.",
            "html": "yago_24409_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Sirikit connected in a marital relationship?",
            "html": "yago_24409_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Bhumibol Adulyadej's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_24409_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Bhumibol Adulyadej's wife?",
            "html": "yago_24409_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24409_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24409_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24409_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24409_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24409_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24409_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24409_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24409_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24409_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24409_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Sirikit is married to Bhumibol Adulyadej\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents suggest that Sirikit met King Bhumibol Adulyadej while they were both living in France, and a relationship developed. They became engaged in 1949 and married in 1950. This sequence of events indicates that Sirikit was indeed married to Bhumibol Adulyadej."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between King Bhumibol Adulyadej and Queen Sirikit, supporting the statement that Sirikit is married to Bhumibol Adulyadej."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}